list25.com 2019-08-12

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. At List25 we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

It is List 25’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, List 25 collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. List 25’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how List 25’s visitors use its website. From time to time, List 25 may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

List 25 also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. List 25 only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to List 25’s websites choose to interact with List 25 in ways that require List 25 to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that List 25 gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive List25 updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, List 25 collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with List 25. List 25 does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

List 25 may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, List 25 may monitor the most popular pages on the lis25.com site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. List 25 may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, List 25 does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

List 25 discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on List 25’s behalf or to provide services available at List 25’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using List 25’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. List 25 will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, List 25 discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when List 25 believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of List 25, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an List 25 website and have supplied your email address, List 25 may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with List 25 and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. List 25 takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. List 25 uses cookies to help List 25 identify and track visitors, their usage of List 25 website, and their website access preferences. List 25 visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using List 25’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of List 25’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**

If List 25, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that List 25 goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of List 25 may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by List 25 and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Not Always Right participates in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. For more information please visit [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website or use our apps. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies for interest based advertising, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website or use our apps. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies for interest based advertising, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

How to opt out  
<http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/>

**Comments**

Comments and other content submitted to Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, List 25 may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in List 25’s sole discretion. List 25 encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
